

DIOGO BRATTI dbratti@gmail.com / +55 48 99951-8667 https://www.linkedin.com/in/diogo-bratti/ https://github.com/diogobratti

FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

Proactive, responsible Javascript and PHP developer focused on mobile and full stack position. Have great soft skills, being an easy person. Known to show strong technical knowledge and to deliver solid systems. More than 4 years experience developing successful systems and 6 years managing IT projects. Active at open source project at GitHub.

SELECTED HIGHLIGHTS

- Successfully managed a major upgrade version at a 10,000 clients software.
- Successfully managed a 17 developers team.
- Cocreated an open source mobile app using React Native and firebase.

| KEY COMPETENCIES | | |
|------------------------|----------------------------|----------------------|
| Software engineering | Team management experience | Agile methodologies |
| Programming | Technical Expertise | Mobile development |
| Full stack development | Open source | Communication skills |

EDUCATION

Universidade do Sul de Santa Catarina (UNISUL), Florianopolis (SC), Brazil IT Projects Management Specialist

Universidade Federal de Santa Catarina (UFSC), Florianopolis (SC), Brazil Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TJSC / Florianopolis (SC), Brazil / September 2011 – present System Analyst (part time)

TJSC (Tribunal de Justiça de Santa Catarina) is a Brazilian State Court. www.tjsc.jus.br

- Utilize extensive software development skills to develop systems in PHP (eproc).
- Supervised a software maintaining contract.
- Successfully leaded a developers team. The team started with 5 developers and ended with 17 developers. The software has 10 thousand users and it was developed in PHP/MySQL (eproc). This software was installed in a year and half.
- Worked as a project manager in a major version software (SAJ) upgrade. The software have 10 thousand users and controls process of a State Court in Brazil.

The software's previous version manage only paper law process. After that, almost all law processes are digital. Later this software was replaced by eproc.

Softplan / Florianopolis (SC), Brazil / February 2010 – September 2011 IT Support

Softplan is a technology developer and supplier. <u>www.softplan.com.br</u>

- Successfully extracted Oracle / DB2 / SQL Server database reports.
- Worked as level 1 support.

Floripa Software / Florianopolis (SC), Brazil / 2009 Software Developer Intern

PERSONAL PROJECT

Open software mobile app to help elder people find someone to take care of them June 2019 – present

With help of 2 parteners, I've built a react native app called "iCare" to help elder people find someone to take care of them. It was developed using react native and Google Firebase backend and authentication. https://github.com/diogobratti/iCare-app

| LANGUAGES | | |
|------------------------|------------------------|--|
| Portuguese - Native | English - Advanced | |
| Spanish – Intermediate | Italian – Intermediate | |

COURSES AND CERTIFICATES

• 3 years of Italian Lessons; Centro de Cultura Italiana: 2006

| ADDITIONAL CREDENTIALS | | |
|-------------------------------|---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------|--|
| TECHNICAL SKILLS | Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) / Oracle / MySQL / Scrum / Visual Studio Code / Git / PHP / React Native / Javascript / Firebase | |
| OTHER ACTIVITIES AND PROJECTS | Work experience program in USA.Open source mobile app at GitHub | |
| HOBBIES AND INTERESTS | Biking | |